jlmpacificepoch.com 2015-06-15

# Pacific Epoch -Privacy Notice

  * [Home](http://pacificepoch.com//china-investment-research/) » 

Pacific Epoch respects the privacy rights of our members and is strongly committed to protecting your privacy online. 

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**

Pacific Epoch collects personal information that you voluntarily provide on this Web site, which may include your name, address, e-mail address, telephone, etc. We use this information to communicate with you and provide you with the appropriate service or product. 

**Disclosure of Personal Information**

Pacific Epoch may disclose your personal information to third parties if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary (a) to comply with the law, court order, government request, or other legal process; (b) to protect the interests, rights, safety, or property of Pacific Epoch or others; (c) to enforce any terms of service on this Web site; or (d) to provide you with the services or products, and to perform other activities related to such services and products, including billing and collection. 

**Accuracy and Security of Personal Information**

To help us protect your privacy, you should maintain the secrecy of the logon ID and password you may have set up in connection with your participation in Pacific Epoch’s services. 

**Accessing and Updating Your Personal Information**

Pacific Epoch members are able to access and change their own personal information at any time via http://www.pacificepoch.com

**Links To Third-Party Web Sites**

Pacific Epoch provides links to third-party Web sites. Pacific Epoch’s privacy policies do not apply to those sites, please take the time to read privacy policies on third-party sites before giving away personal information.
